<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<resources>
    <!-- Fashion -->

    <string name="Charvet_Place_Vendome">The world’s first ever shirt shop, Charvet was founded in 1838.The brand is prominently known for its designs, ready-to-wear shirts, blouses, and suits. Charvet’s rather prestigious clientele include many kings, princes and heads of state.</string>
    <string name="Hermes">Hermes was originally a luxury goods manufacturer. The company was started by Thierry Hermes in 1837. Today it offers ready-to-wear clothing, lifestyle accessories and perfumes. The brand introduced their first women_s shoe collection and the first complete men_s ready-to-wear collection in the 1970s.The silk scarves from Hermes have known to adorn the necks of many celebrities.</string>
    <string name="Coco_Chanel"> Gabrielle Coco Chanel is perhaps the most sought after designer in the world today.The brand forayed into the fashion market with revolutionarychequered bags that took the market by storm.</string>
    <string name="A_P_C">Atelier de Production et de Creation (A.P.C) was established by the renowned designer Jean Touitou in the year 1988. The brand has worked with names like Louis W., Kanye West and Nike. A.P.C is known for the raw jeans they produce, which follow the tradition and employ the trendy factors as well in an appreciably balancing manner.</string>
    <string name="Louis_Vuitton">More popularly known as LV, this French fashion house was named after its creator. Launched in 1854, Louis Vuitton specializes in luxury leather goods, clothing and shoes. The brand is worth $25.9 billion and is endorsed only by the best in the business like Jennifer Lopezand Madonna.</string>
    <string name="Pigallee">he brand is named after the neighborhood of Quartier Pigalle and is established by the designer Stephane Ashpool. Pigalle is known for its street wear inspired by the interests of skaters and hip-hop artists. Recently, Pigalle collaborated with the internationally renowned brand Nike for the production of limited edition sneakers – LeBron 12 Elite.</string>
    <string name="Armor_Lux">Armor lux is French maritime tradition inspired clothing which was founded in the year 1938 in Quimper. Their clothing are known for quality and originality.The standards are maintained in all of their apparel and accessories as well, making it one of the top brands.</string>
    <string name="AMI">In a matter of few years, AMI the establishment of Alexandre Mattiussi became wide-spread because of its casual apparel and the most aesthetic youth designs, especially for teenagers. AMI supplies their products to the most renowned boutiques across the planet and maintain three excellent boutiques in Paris.</string>
    <string name="Tara_Jarmon">Tara Jarmon is an ultimate clothing brand for women. This brand was named after a fashion designer who belonged to Canada. This brand is now one of the top clothing brands in French for women. Tara Jarman now has 80 store-in-store and 23 boutiques throughout Asia and Europe.</string>
    <string name="Comptoir_des_Cotonniers">Comptoir des cotonniers is another top brand that caters to girls’ and their mothers’ clothing. This brand is a full wardrobe which has clothing for every occasion. Comptoir des cotonniers said to be the top brands that pioneers luxury at an affordable price.</string>


    <!-- Restaurant -->
    <string name="Le_Meurice">Anyone wanting a grand-slam experience of Gallic gastronomic grandeur won"t do better than the glamorous dining room at the Hotel Meurice in the heart of the city. Though it was redecorated by Philippe Starck several years ago, it's good French bones survived intact – mosaic floor, crystal chandeliers, heavy damask curtains at the windows overlooking the Tuileries Gardens across the street – and the magnificent space is animated by old-school but friendly service that's as precise as a minuette.</string>
    <string name="L_Astrance">Despite the vertiginous prices of Paris haute cuisine, a meal at one of these nec plus ultra tables is an investment that just can"t disappoint, and snagging a sought-after table at chef Pascal Barbot's three-star restaurant on a cobbled side street in the 16th arrondissement is well worth persistence. The smallest and most casual table at the top of the Parisian food chain, this high-ceilinged dining room with mirrored walls, widely spaced tables and friendly service offers a decidedly 21st-century take on French haute cuisine</string>
    <string name="Huitrerie_Regis">Tucked away in the heart of Saint Germain des Pres, this snug shop-front table with a white facade and interior is the best place in Paris for a fix of impeccably fresh oysters, which are delivered directly from France"s Marennes-Oléron region on the Atlantic coast. Depending upon availability, prawns, clams and sea urchins can also be added to your plateau de fruits de mer, which will be served with bread and butter.</string>
    <string name="Macéo">Run by Englishman Mark Williamson – whose Willi"s Wine Bar around the corner is a favourite local bolthole for Parisian oenophiles – this handsome restaurant with oxblood walls, wedding cake mouldings and parquet floors overlooks the Palais Royal in the heart of Paris. Chef Thierry Bourbonnais not only includes many vegetable dishes on his menu – making this a good choice for vegetarians – but features regularly changing tasting menus themed around a single vegetable, such as asparagus or tomatoes</string>
    <string name="Spring">Ever since Chicago-born chef Daniel Rose moved from the 9th arrondissement to a renovated 17th-century house in Les Halles in July 2010, he"s been playing to a packed house with his inventive cuisine du marche menu. This talented American shows off just how cosmopolitan the city's culinary talent pool has become, and Parisians have been swooning over dishes such as Basque country trout with avocado and coriander flowers and grilled New Caledonian prawns on a bed of shaved baby fennel.</string>
    <string name="Les_Tablettes">Signalling a revival of the serious, dressed-up restaurant in Paris (which had lost out as a vehicle for young chefs going out on their own in favour of the bistro) chef Jean-Louis Nomicos"s new table in the swanky 16th arrondissement has a dramatic modern basket-weave interior by French interior designer Anne-Cécile Comar and a dog's leg banquette upholstered in apricot velvet.</string>
    <string name="Le_Stella">Since most of Paris"s storied brasseries are now owned by corporate chains and serve wiltingly mediocre food, it's a pleasure to head to one of the last remaining independent ones in a quiet corner of the silk-stocking 16th arrondissement for a fine feed of such well-prepared French classics as onion soup, escargots, sole meunière, steak tartare, roast lamb and other Gallic standards.</string>
    <string name="Thoumieux">Previously head chef at the glamorous Les Ambassadeurs at the Hotel de Crillon, chef Jean-Francois Piège went out on his own two years ago when he rebooted Thoumieux, a long-running Left Bank brasserie known for its cassoulet and huge resident cat. While the new menu and slick Manhattan supper club décor at this address created a lot of buzz, this gastronomically witty young chef"s talent was never really on display here until he opened an intimate first-floor restaurant with a Las Vegas, rat-pack decor by Parisian interior designer India Mahdavi at the same address last autumn.</string>
    <string name="Yam_Tcha">After training with chef Pascal Barbot at the three-star L"Astrance, young Burgundy-born cook Adeline Grattard – one of the still rare female chefs in Paris – did a stint in Hong Kong during which she fell in love with Asian produce and cooking techniques and met her husband Chiwah, who works as the tea steward (as an alternative to wine, you can be served a different tea with every course of your meal here)</string>
    <string name="Ze_Kitchen_Galerie">Styled like the neighbouring art galleries on this Saint Germain des Pres side street, this loft-like white space with parquet floors is furnished with steel tables and chairs and decorated with contemporary art. Chef William Ledeuil"s popular restaurant offers an intriguing experience of contemporary French cooking. Ledeuil, who trained with Guy Savoy, is fascinated by Asia and makes imaginative use of oriental herbs and ingredients in original dishes like Sardinian malloreddus pasta with a pesto of Thai herbs, parmesan cream and green olive condiment, or grilled monkfish with an aubergine marmelade and Thai-seasoned sauce vierge. </string>

    <!-- Attraction Places -->
    <string name="Seine_Cruise">The River Seine runs nearly 800 km (500 miles) through France on its way to the English Channel. Cruising the river as it winds through Paris is one of the most romantic things visitors can do. Seine cruises pass under numerous bridges in Paris, going by such sights as the Louvre, Notre Dame Cathedral and the Eiffel Tower. A Seine cruise lasts about an hour, but what a magic hour it is! A Seine cruise also is a good way to experience Paris at night.</string>
    <string name="Place_des_Vosges">The Place des Vosges, formerly called Place Royale, was the prototype for all residential squares in Europe. All houses were built using the same design: red brick with steep pitched blue slate roofs. Not only is it shaped like a true square, it is the first city square that was planned by a monarch (Henry IV in the early 17th century). Third, it turned the Marais into a fashionable spot for French nobility in the decades before the French Revolution.</string>
    <string name="Moulin_Rouge">The year 1889 is known as the year when France’s most famous landmark, the Eiffel Tower, was constructed. It’s also the year the Moulin Rouge opened its doors as an entertainment venue. When it opened, it catered to the rich who wanted to “slum” it. Courtesans worked there and were responsible for inventing the can-can, a dance considered racy for the era. The Moulin Rouge is still considered Paris’s premier entertainment venue and has been the subject of numerous films.</string>
    <string name="Conciergerie">The Conciergerie was built in the 10th century to be the main palace for French kings who, over the centuries, enlarged it. Its Great Hall was one of the largest in Europe; another hall was where the palace’s 2,000 workers ate. Some buildings were converted into a prison in the 14th century. The palace later became a revolutionary tribunal and prison during the Reign of Terror, with famous prisoners including Marie Antoinette and Madame du Barry. Today the Conciergerie is a popular tourist attraction in Paris but also still serves as courts.</string>
    <string name="Pantheon">The Pantheon is where famous French citizens are buried. Modeled after the Pantheon in Rome, it was originally a church dedicated to St. Genevieve, the patron saint of Paris, and her relics. The church was rebuilt in the neoclassical style by King Louis XV to thank God for his recovery from serious illness. It was changed to a mausoleum during the French Revolution to honor revolutionary martyrs. Famous people buried here include Voltaire, Victor Hugo and Marie Curie.</string>
    <string name="Pere_Lachaise_Cemetery">The world’s most visited cemetery, Pere Lachaise became a municipal cemetery in 1804 under Napoleon. It is the final resting place for many famous people, including the Doors’ Jim Morrison, author Oscar Wilde and chanteuse Edith Piaf. The cemetery contains many sculptures, as each family of the deceased tried to out-do the monuments placed by the other wealthy families. The result is many spectacular works of art that are equally as interesting as the various gravesites of famous individuals.</string>
    <string name="Disneyland_aris">When Europeans can’t get to Los Angeles to see the original Disneyland, they head to Disneyland Paris, the most visited theme park in Europe. Just like its namesake, Disneyland Paris is more than just a theme park with spectacular rides. It’s a resort with hotels, shopping and golf among its varied activities. In 1992, it became the second Disney park to open outside of the United States. It’s located about 30 km (20 miles) from central Paris. A companion park, Walt Disney Studios Park, opened in 2002.</string>
    <string name="Musee_de_l_Orangerie">Travelers who appreciate impressionist and post-impressionist art need to check out the Musee de l’Orangerie. The museum, located in a corner of the Tuilries Garden, is home to eight Water Lilies murals by Claude Monet; these murals are considered the museum’s centerpiece. It also contains works by other impressionist artists, including Picasso, Renoir, Cezanne, Matisse and Modigliani. The orangerie was originally built in 1852 to protect the Tuileries Palace’s orange trees.</string>
    <string name="Palais_Garnier">Architect Charles Garnier spared no ornate detail when he designed the Palais Garnier in the 19th century. Perhaps this is why the building was the most expensive of its era. Seating nearly 2,000 people, the Palais Garnier is home to the National Opera of Paris. It is the star of the novel and subsequent films, Phantom of the Opera. The Palais Garnier is still in use today though mainly for ballet and also is home to the opera library museum.</string>
    <string name="Les_Invalides">Les Invalides is a complex of buildings that honors the French military. It was built in 1670 as a hospital and retirement home for vets. It still serves that function today as well as many more. Les Invalides is home to military museums and a church that is the burial site of its war heroes, including Napoleon Bonaparte. Les Invalides is where rioters obtained the cannons and muskets they used later that day to storm the Bastille, thus kicking off the French Revolution.</string>

    <!-- Praks -->
    <string name="Jardin_des_Tuileries">The impeccably formal Garden of the Tuileries were designed and laid out from 1640 by André Le Nôtre along the Historical Axis that he started to trace. From the Place du Carrousel, the Tuileries Garden offer an unbroken vista towards the Place de la Concorde, the Arc de Triomphe and the Grande Arche. It remains the largest and oldest public garden in Paris today.</string>
    <string name="Jardin_du_Luxembourg">Among the many parks and gardens of Paris, the Luxembourg Garden is certainly one of the favourite green places of Parisians, students and tourists. Fascinated by this oxygen bottle in the centre of the capital, visitors enjoy the greenery punctuated with a multitude of statues, playgrounds and the famous Guignol puppet show.</string>
    <string name="Parc_Monceau">Parc Monceau is situated in the 8th arrondissement and covers an area of 8.2 hectares. Landscaped in the 18th century with many follies (Corinthian pillars, an Egyptian pyramid), Parc Monceau was restored during the Second Empire in an English style made up of curved walkways and randomly placed statues. The public garden is a very popular play area for children residing locally.</string>
    <string name="Jardin_des_Plantes">More than just a public garden, the Jardin des Plantes is the main botanical garden in France. Situated in the 5th arrondissement on the Left Bank, the garden was created in 1626 under the name of “Jardin du Roi” (Garden of the King). The garden features historic glasshouses, a maze (le labyrinthe), a small zoo and a beautiful rose garden.?</string>
    <string name="Jardin_des_Champs_Élysées">The lower section of the avenue des Champs-Élysées, from the Place de la Concorde to the Rond Point des Champs-Élysées, is bordered on each side by the English gardens designed by the architect Hittorff (1838). Consisting of lawns, beautiful conker trees and shrubberies, they blend harmoniously with the pleasure pavilions.</string>
    <string name="Champ_de_Mars">The green esplanade of the Champ de Mars spreads between the classical façade of the École Militaire and the famous Eiffel Tower. The park is named after the Roman god of war: Campus Martius (Field of Mars). The vast esplanade welcomed the World Exhibitions of 1867, 1878, 1889, 1900, and 1937. Anywhere you sit in the park you will have a majestic view of the Eiffel Tower – so grand that you will never forget it!</string>
    <string name="Parc_des_Buttes_Chaumont">The public park of Buttes-Chaumont was created in a former gypsum and limestone quarry by Baron Haussmann between 1864 and 1867 to serve the growing population of the 19th and 20th arrondissements. The English landscape park features a grotto, waterfalls and a romantic Roman temple on the top of a promontory known as the Temple de la Sibylle, which is a miniature version of the Temple of Vesta in Tivoli, Italy.</string>
    <string name="Cimetière_du_Père_Lachaise">Against all odds, the Père Lachaise Cemetery in the east of Paris is one of the favourite green place to Parisians and tourists alike. The largest cemetery of the City of Paris, Père Lachaise is also the first garden cemetery and greatly differs from other similar places such as the Montmartre or Montparnasse cemeteries. Along the promenade, visitors can discover the graves of many celebrities: Guillaume Apollinaire, Honoré de Balzac, Sarah Bernhardt, Maria Callas, Frédéric Chopin, Jean de la Fontaine, Molière, Jim Morrison, Édith Piaf, Marcel Proust, and Oscar Wilde. </string>
    <string name="Lac_inférieur_Bois_de_Boulogne">The large public park of Bois de Boulogne along the western edge of Paris was commissioned by Napoleon III between 1852 and 1858. Like its eastern counterpart, Bois de Vincennes, the large woodland includes an English landscape garden. The Lac Inférieur is the largest artificial lake of the park and includes an island accessible by boat on which stands a small wooden kiosk known as the Kiosk of the Emperor. Beautiful trees, small boats, swans and ducks, contribute to the picturesque and romantic scene of the place.</string>
    <string name="Lac_Daumesnil_Bois_de_Vincennes">Paris’ largest public park, the Bois de Vincennes was landscaped between 1855 and 1866 under the reign of Emperor Napoleon III. The artificial Daumesnil Lake is set in a beautiful English garden and includes two islands on which stand a Temple of Love and a Swiss Chalet.</string>
</resources>